2009年 你们的Robin阿姨得到一份\n主持早间节目的工作
Back 2009, your aunt Robin got\na job hosting a morning show.
这意味着她要早起
Which meant she had to\nget up kind of early.
有多早呢?
How early?
大家早
Morning,everybody.
嘿  Robin
Hey,Robin.
你真的这么干了 啊?
So you're actually doing it,huh?
你真是凌晨2点就去上班啊
You're actually going\nto work at 2:00 a.m.
我做这些可不是为了自己\n是为了我的粉丝
I'm not doing it for me.\nI'm doing it for the fans.
谁会是凌晨4点播出的节目的粉丝啊?
Who exactly are the fans of a show\nthat airs at 4:00 in the morning?
凌晨5点的节目主持人吧?
People getting up to host a\nshow at 5:00 in the morning?
还没电视卖了的瘾君子?
Meth addicts who haven't\nsold their TVs yet?
刚刚下班 还没叫醒孩子上学的脱衣舞女?
Strippers in that messy gray area between getting\noff work and getting their kids up for school?
反正他们支持我
Them's my peeps.
好啦 告诉我\n最近有啥好玩的吗?
All right, catch me up.\nWhat's been going on?
你知道的 平平淡淡而已
You know,the yoozh.
- 真的吗  平平淡淡? \n- 没错
Really,the yoozh? Yes.
Robin 想着你见过的最滑稽的事
Robin,think of the funniest\nthing that has ever happened.
明白了
Got it.
想象比这双倍的滑稽
Now double that.
一头黑猩猩穿了两件晚礼服?
So a chimpanzee wearing two tuxedos?
Marshall今天发生了比这还搞笑的事
Something even funnier than\nthat happens to Marshall today.
好的 首先\n没有比这更搞笑的了
Okay,first of all,there's\nnothing funnier than that.
然后 瞧 \n这并不是什么好故事
Second of all,look, it's\nnot that good a story.
哦 好啦 大伙
Oh,come on,you guys.
你们这四个住在地球上最棒的城市里\n年轻活泼的家伙们
You're four young active people living\nin the most exciting city on earth.
你们竟没啥好玩的事要跟我说?
You telling me you\nhave no stories for me?
我能说啥呢? 这几周就是这么过的
What can I say? Some\nweeks are just like that.
每天重复一样的事
It's the same thing over and over.
我班里的一个小孩喝了一些胶水
A kid in my class ate some paste.
我耍伎俩骗一个傻妞跟我约会
I used deceitful means to hook up\nwith a less-than-intelligent girl.
我的前女友Karen搬到城里来了
My ex-girlfriend Karen moved to town.
就是 就是没啥新鲜的 Robin
It's just, it's all the same,Robin.
Karen搬来城里了?
Karen's in town?
- 你不是开玩笑的吧!\n- 不!
- You have got to be kidding me!\n- No!
孩子们 我想我跟你们提过Karen了
Kids,I think I've told you about Karen.
她是我高中的女友 我们分分合合
She was my girlfriend in high school,\nand intermittently through college.
她很漂亮 人又聪明
She was beautiful,smart.
我非常爱她
I was madly in love with her.
但问题是\nMarshall和Lily不喜欢她
The only problem was,\nMarshall and Lily were not.
我想这跟Karen的这张嘴有关系
I think it had something to do with\nevery time Karen opened her mouth.
我喜欢你们住在这种集体宿舍里\n这真是美国特色的啊
I love that you guys live\nin a dorm. It's so American.
感觉就像我们都吃着三明治\n搞起种族歧视来（美国特色）
It's like,let's all eat baloney\nsandwiches and be racist.
哦 天啊 她简直就是个垃圾
Oh,my God,she was such a douche.
伙计 她简直是Massengill的继承人\n（暗喻Karen嘴贱）
Dude,she was the heiress\nto the Massengill fortune.
她没那么坏
She really wasn't that bad.
你当然这么想啦
Of courseyouthink that.
她把你也给带坏了
She turned you into one\nof her douche zombies.
我要吃掉你的脑袋\n只吃有机和喂草长成的
I want to eat your brain, but\nonly if it's organic and grass-fed.
什么啊?
What?
给我递一下盐好吗?
Will you pass the salt?
盐?
Salt?
真小资
So bourgeois.
没错
Totally.
那是什么?
What's that thing?
那是电视机 Karen
That's a TV,Karen.
我不看电视的
I don't watch TV.
没错
Totally.
你真以为我买了票去看摔角狂热赛?
You thought I actually bought\ntickets to WrestleMania?
我说的反话而已
I was being ironic.
没错
Totally.
我知道你说的是反话
I know that you were being ironic.
我这样也不过是为了嘲讽一下而已
I too am being ironic.
咱们冲吧!
Let's do this!
什么?
What?
那身装扮我花了一个月才洗下来
That makeup didn't come off for a month.
我那时还要去见Lily的父母
I had to meet Lily's parents that way.
我从没那么白痴过
I've never looked like a bigger jackass.
直到今天为止
Until today.
讲你的故事 讲你的故事 讲你的故事...
Tell the story. Tell the\nstory. Tell the story...
就放过我吧!
Just let it go!
哦 够了 这很好玩吗?
Well,hold on. Is it really funny?
Robin 我可不是唬你啊
Robin,I am not kidding you.
我都不想让你听它\n因为真的 你这一生中
I almost don't want you to hear it, because\nseriously, for the rest of your life,
都不会再遇到比这更搞笑的事了\n你会诅咒自己的
nothing else will ever be as\nfunny and you will curse yourself
咒骂自己为啥一开始要听这个事
for agreeing to ever hear\nit in the first place.
但说真的 你一定要听\n真的很搞笑
But seriously,you got to\nhear it. It's so funny.
好吧
Fine.
今早我在公司的球馆打篮球
I was at the company gym this\nmorning playing basketball.
我的同事挖苦人可是一点不留情的
The guys I work with can be\npretty brutal with their ridicule.
嘿 瞧Wisniewski那孬样
Hey,look at Wisniewski.
他要哭鼻子了 瞧他
He's gonna cry. Look at him.
瞧他那样
Yeah,look at him.
我不明白 我觉得膝盖也许真扭伤了
I don't know. I don't think knees\naren't supposed to bend that way.
我想他可能伤到前交叉韧带了
I think he might have tore his ACL.
伙计 \n他伤到的只能是子宫颈和处女膜吧
Bro,the only thing that guy tore\nwas his cervix or maybe his hymen.
或者是输卵管吧 嘣!
Or his Fallopian tube. Boom!
我已经对对话进行过过滤处理
I may have cleaned up\nthe dialogue a little bit.
然后...
Anyways...
我拿起储物袋子取出工作服...
I go to my duffle bag to\nget out my work clothes...
等等等等 \n让我来说 让我来说 让我来说
Wait,wait,wait,wait. I want to say\nit. I want to say it. I want to say it.
好吧 你说吧
Fine. You say it.
Marshall拿起储物袋子取出他的工作服\n然后...
Marshall goes to his duffle bag\nto get out his work clothes, and...
不不不不 你来说吧\n你说起来更搞笑
No,no,no, you say it.\nIt's funnier if you say it.
不 让我来说 不不不 你来说吧\n你说 你说吧
No,let me say it. No,no,you\nsay it. You say it. Say it.
从刚才那里说起
Same time.
不不不不 你说 你说
No,no,no,you go. You go.
- 我忘了...\n- Marshall忘了拿裤子!
- I forgot...\n- Marshall forgot his pants!
他忘了拿裤子
He forgot his pants.
老爸老妈浪漫史\n第四季第16集
How I Met Your\nMother Season04 Episode16
好吧 Marshall没穿裤子\n真好笑啊
Okay,Marshall forgot his\npants. That's pretty funny.
不如黑猩猩穿两件礼服搞笑
It's no chimpanzee wearing two tuxedos.
我是说 它怎么能... \n怎么能忘了它已经穿了一件了呢?
I mean,what did he... he\nforgot he put the first one on?
傻猴子\n(汗 是猩猩啊)
Stupid monkey.
Karen回到纽约来了 \n很奇怪 对吧?
So Karen in New York. Weird,right?
Ted 你不能再吃Karen这棵回头草了啊
Ted,you cannot get back\ntogether with Karen.
我可没说要跟她旧情复燃啊
I never said I was going to\nget back together with her.
我只是在想 她对城里不熟
But I was thinking, she's new in town.
我给她打个电话也不是什么恐怖的事嘛?
Would it be the worst thing in\nthe world if I gave her a call?
不 不 Ted 这不是什么最恐怖的事
No,no,Ted,it wouldn't be\nthe worst thing in the world.
这是世上第四大最恐怖的事
It would be the fourth worst thing.
第一是火山大爆发\n第二是行星撞地球
**Super volcano. **An\nasteroid hits the Earth.
第三是电影飞车人生就此失传了\n第四是Ted给Karen打电话
**All footage of Evel Knievel\nis lost. **Ted calls Karen.
第五是Lily被鲨鱼吃了
**Lily gets eaten by a shark.
我就是Lily\n我敢保证这个排序的公正性
I'm Lily and I approve\nthe order of that list.
你们可是不知道内情哇
You don't know the whole story.
Ted和Karen整日在校园里出双入对\n天天如此
Ted and Karen were off and on all through\ncollege, and it always went the same way.
他们一起玩 恶心来恶心去的\n直到有一天...
They'd be having fun, douching\nit up, and then one day...
我知道你认为烤胡椒香肠口味是最棒的\n你说得完全没错 所以我...
I know you think pepperoni is fascist\nand you're totally right,so I...
哦 天啊! Karen!
Oh,my God! Karen!
对不起啦 老兄
Sorry,bro.
在你发飙之前 \n我想你该去读一读波德莱尔的"恶之花"
Before you say anything, I think that you\nshould read Baudelaire's Les Fleurs du Mal.
好吧
Okay.
然后他们分手了
So then they break up.
Ted很消沉\n我们俩在等待时机
Ted would be all depressed and we would\nwait the appropriate amount of time
然后告诉他我们的看法
and then we'd would tell\nhim how we really felt.
我和Karen分手了
Karen and I broke up.
- 我们恨死她!\n- 贱人快滚!
- We hated her!\n- Bitch had to go!
然后他痛下决心\n还搭了巴士去普罗维登斯
And then Ted would build up a head of\nsteam and finally take the bus to Providence
去跟Karen摊牌
to give Karen a piece of his mind.
- 怎么样了?\n- 好极了
- How'd it go?\n- Great.
看看谁回来了
Look who's back.
- Karen\n- Karen\n- Karen.\n- Karen.
然后 毫无悬念 故事重演
And then,sure enough, the whole\nthing would start all over again.
发出比"一万个疯子乐队"还疯2回的叫声吧\n因为我买到了Natalie Merchant演唱会的门票...\n(一个著名的摇滚乐队以及主唱)
Make that 10,002 Maniacs, because\nI got us Natalie Merchant tick...
对不起啦 老兄
Sorry,bro.
她来学校找你\n这次你又不在
So she would come visit you at school\nand the second you turned your back
她就带男人去你宿舍?
she would bring guys\nback toyourdorm room?
真牛
Respect.
好啦 我是个白痴
Okay,I was an idiot.
她是我的第一个女朋友\n我那时很爱很爱她
She was my first real girlfriend.\nI was madly in love with her.
我们在大学里都干过些后悔的事
We all did stuff we regret in college.
大三时 Marshall交了一个哥们\n总戴着一顶棉线帽 让大家管他叫M.J.Smooth\n(模仿迈克尔.杰克逊的'smooth criminal犯罪高手")
Junior year Marshall grew a soul patch, wore a\nrasta hat, and asked everyone to call him M.J.Smooth.
我可从没为这事后悔过
I don't regret that for one second.
你们真的觉得我不该打给她?
So you guys absolutely don't\nthink I should call her?
- Ted 不要\n- 你就断了这念头吧
- Ted,no.\n- Get it through your thick skull.
好啦 好啦 我不会的
Okay,okay,fine, I won't.
搞笑的是 我已经打过了
Interesting piece of\ntrivia: I called her.
- 你个白痴!\n- 你搞什么鬼啊?
- You idiot!\n- What are you doing?
裤子的事
The pants story.
我真不敢相信你打给她了
I can't believe you called her.
你为啥不干脆在电话里\n约她出来吃午饭算了?
Why don't you just ask her\nto lunch while you're at it?
因为Lily 我不会叫她出来吃午饭了... \n下一次就不会了
Because,Lily, I'm not going to\nask her out to lunch... again.
你约她吃午饭了?
You asked her to lunch?
有谁会跟旧情人吃午饭啊?
Why would anyone want to\nhave lunch with their ex?
你这个问题问得好 Marshall
Glad you asked,Marshall.
有四种原因促使"与旧情人吃午餐"的发生
There are four possible\nmotives behind an "ex lunch."
第一 他们想复合
They want to get back together.
哦 跟我的高中男友Scooter一个德行
Oh,like my high school\nboyfriend Scooter.
百合啊 真有心\n(和Lily名字一样的花)
Lilies,clever.
抱歉 我可没有踏板车送给你\n(和Scooter一样的名字)
I'm sorry I don't\nhave a scooter for you.
天啊 真搞笑!\n都忘了你这么幽默了
My God,that's funny!\nForgot how funny you are.
- 服务员在哪儿呢?\n- 为什么? 你喜欢服务员?
- Where is that waiter?\n- Why? You like waiters?
我可以去做服务员
I can be a waiter.
我要做世上最好的服务员\n这样你就会爱我了
I'm going to be the greatest waiter\non this earth, and then you'll love me.
第二 他们想灭了你
They want to kill you.
跟我和Wendy吃午饭一样
Like when I had lunch with Wendy.
我很高兴我们终于可以一起吃饭了
I'm glad we could finally do this.
你知道么 当你第九次把我们的约会推后\n我都要放弃了
You know,after the ninth time you\nrescheduled on me, I almost gave up on you.
但你没有 你坚持不懈
But you didn't. You just kept on trying.
另外 我有样东西一直想给你
By the way,there's something\nI've been meaning to give you.
枪! 她有枪!
Gun! She's got a gun!
是...是条领带
It-it's a tie.
第三 他们想归还你的东西
They actually do want to\ngive you your stuff back.
像我和Curt吃午餐一样
Like when I had lunch with Curt.
另外 我有样东西要给你
By the way,there's something\nI've been meaning to give you.
我的点38短管左轮手枪!
My snub-nosed. 38 police special!
我知道我给弄丢了
I knew I left that somewhere.
每次我看新闻 \n我都在想 "哦 希望这不是用的我的枪"
Every time I watch the news, I'm\nlike, "Oops,hope that wasn't my gun."
跟你分手是对的
Breaking up was the right choice.
或者是第四是炫耀他们的近况
Or #4: to rub your face\nin how great they're doing.
像我和Nicole Barsamian吃午餐一样
Like my lunch with Nicole Barsamian.
- Nicole Barsamian是谁?\n- 我的前女友
- Who's Nicole Barsamian?\n- My ex.
你好 Nicole\n( 真有历史)
Hello,Nicole.
你看着不错  Marshall\n(小Marshall好可爱)
You look well,Marshall.
你也是 我觉得
You look okay,I guess.
- 我跟别人约会了 \n- 这么快? 谁啊 ?
- I'm seeing someone.\n- Already? Who?
Lee Roberts
他能读懂5年级的课本了
Lee Roberts. He reads\nat a fifth grade level.
你一定要取消这个午餐约会
You have to cancel the lunch.
我一定会这么做的 绝对...
I would definitely\ndo that, definitely...
可我们已经吃过了
except I already had it.
Robin 我要借你的枪托用用
Robin,I'm going to need to\nborrow the butt of your gun.
可我又把弄它丢了 简直难以置信
I actually lost it again.\nCan you believe that?
咋能和那女人一起用餐呢?
How could break bread with that woman?
只是午餐 况且她也没吃小麦
It was just lunch,and you\nknow she doesn't eat wheat.
我们谈笑风生
We had a great time catching up.
甚至还拿以前的幼稚行为开涮
We even laughed about what\njerks we were back then.
真不敢相信我每天都顶着个贝雷帽
I can't believe I had a beret\nfor each day of the week.
真不敢相信我在背包上\n印了个莫里哀(法国喜剧作家 演员)
I can't believe I had an iron-on\nimage of Moli? re on my backpack.
哥们 我们那时都自命不凡
Man,we were pretentious.
太自命不凡了
So pretentious.
请问点什么?
What can I get you?
我不想太张扬 \n但是你们把"教皇新堡"葡萄酒
Um, I don't want to cause a scene, but\nyour wine list has a Chteauneuf-du-Pape
排在了"普罗旺斯山谷"葡萄酒下面
listed under the "Ctes du Provence."
你该提醒下你们的侍酒师
You might want to alert your sommelier.
你呢?
And for you?
我讨厌看菜单 就来些\n意式芝士烤面包?
I hate to go off-menu, but can you bring\nus somebruschett with freshmozzarell?
谢谢(意大利语)
Grazie.
真不错 真不错
It was great. It was great.
我是说 其间只有一会儿不自在
I mean,there was one weird\nmoment towards the end.
嗯 那你当时咋和她告别?
Yeah,how do you say\ngood-bye in those situations?
亲下脸蛋太没创意
A kiss on the cheek is too familiar.
而握手言别又太正式
A handshake is too formal.
拥抱就像没快感没创意的性交
And a hug is just\nlike a public dry hump.
我觉得你理解错了
I think you're hugging wrong.
那咋告别的?
So what happened?
好吧...
Well...
叔本华自认为...
Schopenhauer made a saucy little\nargument in which he posited...
Ted 亲爱的 我要你出去啃路沿\n我马上就出来检查
Ted,honey,I want you to go outside and\nbite the curb. I'll be out in a minute.
嘿 Karen是我的初恋 好不?
Hey,Karen was the first\ngirl I ever loved. Okay?
时隔境迁 我-我不明白
And after the year I've had, I\n- I don't know,
也许与她共进午餐\n让我回忆起过往的青葱岁月
I guess having lunch with her just\nreminded me of what it was like to be 18
并且认清人生的真谛
and have my whole life figured out.
还有我要提醒大家\n至少我是穿着裤子 Marshall
And I would like to remind everyone that\nat least I was wearing pants,Marshall.
不! 不! 你不能这样转变话题
No! No,no,no! You can't just go\nchanging the subject like that.
对呀 裤子糗事
Oh,yeah,the pants story.
裤子糗事干掉他! 裤子糗事干掉他!\n(bomaye拳击比赛用语)
Pants story bomaye! Pants story bomaye!
没啥糗事!
There's no story!
我碰到了点状况 所以打Lily电话
I had a little situation,\nso I called Lily.
再说遍 啥状况啊?
And just refresh us;\nwhat was that situation?
我忘带裤子了
I forgot my pants.
忘带裤子是啥意思?
What do you mean you forgot your pants?
我忘记拿了
I forgot them.
我要你给我送过来
Now,I need you to bring me some.
你的备用裤子呢?
What about your spare pants?
上周四的芥末事件
Last Thursday, the mustard incident.
天哪 你真是个金鱼脑袋\n(金鱼的记忆只有3秒)
Jeez,woman,you have the\nmemory of a goldfish.
不 Ted 你那事绝不会那么简单
No,Ted,you're not getting off that easy.
Marshall的裤子糗事 还有点笑料...
Marshall's pants story, while amusing...
才有点笑料? 是笑爆掉吧
Amusing? Try very amusing.
比起Karen的事 这根本不值一提\n先把你的故事讲完
Is nothing compared to this\nKaren madness. Finish your story.
咋了? 就这些\n只是在餐馆里啵了下而已
What? That's it. It was just\none kiss in the restaurant.
为啥特地指明"在餐馆里"
Why did you say "in the restaurant?"
你们还在哪里啵了?
Did you kiss somewhere else?
譬如说 在树上?
Like where,in a tree?
没 Lily 我们可没在树上干
No,Lily,we did not make out in a tree.
这家伙咋了?
What's with this one?
Ted 你做啥了?
Oh,Ted. What did you do?
Ted 你咋能这样?
Ted,how could you?
Ted 即使Marshall今天忘带裤子上班
Ted,Marshall forgot to bring\nhis pants to work today,
在我们几个里 你仍旧最傻帽
and you're still the\nstupidest person at this table.
好吧 Lily 老实说
Okay,Lily,let's be honest.
我们都知道你的真正动机
We both know your real motivation here.
你很Karen是因为她流连忘返
You hate Karen because she lingered.
你这狗娘养的
You son of a bitch.
流连忘返是啥意思?
What do you mean she lingered?
1998年2月5日 我正在画画...
February 5,1998. I was painting...
抱歉 我... 抱歉 我...
Oh,sorry. I... Sorry. I...
你的调色板有梵高早期的风范\n你不觉得吗?
You know,that color palette is a bit\nderivative of early Van Gogh, don't you think?
背着Ted乱搞 批评我的画\n随她咋样都不关我鸟事
Cheat on Ted, criticize my painting,\nwhatever,that's your business.
但我看见你偷窥我男人的下三寸\n还流连忘返?
But I catch you peeping on\nmy man's junk and youlinger?
真是活腻了
You gots to get got.
别太较真
The game is the game.
容我为Karen找个理由\n那时候我刚锻炼完身体
In Karen's defense,\nI had just worked out.
那你为啥要画Marshall的裸体?
Why'd you have to paint\nMarshall nude anyway?
因为他吃光了我的水果
Because he ate my bowl of fruit.
听着 重点是Karen色迷迷地流连忘返
Look,the point is,\nKaren is a dirty linger,
你不能再把她带到我们的生活中来了
and you cannot bring\nher back into our lives.
放心吧 就那晚而已!
Relax,it was just that one night!
还有之后三晚外加一个早晨
And the next three after\nthat. And one morning.
但至少我穿着裤子 Marshall
But at least I had pants on,Marshall.
事实上 我没穿
Although,actually,I didn't.
等下 你把她带到我们公寓了?
Wait,this happened in our apartment?
当时我在哪?
Where was I?
那些帮你调整新生物钟的安眠药?
You know those sleeping pills you're\ntaking to keep on your crazy new schedule?
我想它们的药劲比你想的强多了
I think they're stronger\nthan you realize.
拉方丹把球传给特金
LaFontaine gets the puck to Turgeon.
特金射门 被守门员接住了
Turgeon shoots. Glove save.
嘿 Ted 嘿 Lily
Hey,Ted. Hey,Lily.
别担心 我不会告诉Marshall的
Don't worry. I won't tell Marshall.
我要拿罐啤酒 你要不?
I'm gonna grab a beer. You want one?
啤酒 我刚想倒葡萄酒来着
Beer. I'll start decanting the Bordeaux.
Ted 回想过去确实很有趣\n那时你是个散发处女味稚嫩农场妞
Ted,sure it's fun to look back at a time when you\nwere a fresh-faced farm girl with a virgin's glow.
但那些东西--俄亥俄州\nKaren 大学 发生在BS
But all that stuff--\nOhio,Karen,college-- all that was BS.
"Stinson出现前"
"Before Stinson."
但现在你生活得丰富多彩!
Now your life is awesome!
我是说 你还和\n前女友住在一起 真荒唐
I mean,yeah,you still live with your\nex-girlfriend, which is ridiculous.
你的光剑(星球大战中的武器)\n虚无缥缈
Your laser tag chops\nare almost nonexistent.
看看你的衣橱 \n难道你还对优质面料过敏?
And your wardrobe, it's like,what,\nare you allergic to quality fabrics?
说真的 Ted 好自为之
Seriously,Ted,shape up.
我们说啥来着?
What were we talking about?
这女人接下来咋了?
So what's next with this broad?
拜托 故事已经完了
Oh,please, the story's already written.
Ted是想方设法踢球的\nCharlie Brown 而Karen是Lucy
Ted is Charlie Brown trying to\nkick the football and Karen's Lucy,
在最后关头抢走了球 和它做爱
who pulls it away at the last\nsecond and has sex with it.
你们知道我的意思
You guys know what I mean.
Ted将会陷入爱河 而Karen\n会背着他和那些只会说
Ted's gonna fall in love, and then Karen's gonna\ncheat on him with some meathead, who's like...
"抱歉 伙计"的傻帽乱搞
"Sorry,bro."
错 错 错!
Wrong,wrong,wrong!
你把正确答案忘在你裤子里了吧 Marshall
You must have left the right\nanswer in your pants, Marshall,
因为事情绝非如此
because that's exactly\nwhat didn't happen.
事情是这样的
Because here's what happened.
一天下午 我们在Karen的住所...
One afternoon, we were\nat Karen's place...
Karen? 我的天
Karen? Oh,my God.
你咋能这样?
How could you?
抱歉 伙计
Sorry,bro.
所以这次 和Karen乱搞的傻帽
So this time, the meathead\nKaren was cheating with
是我 Ted 我 Ted
was me,Ted. Me, Ted.
记得Marshall忘带裤子吗?
Remember that time\nMarshall forgot his pants?
妈的 Ted!
Damn it,Ted!
别再转变话题 你太过分了
You quit trying to change the\nsubject. You crossed the line.
你们合伙伤害了那可怜人的心
You are complicit in breaking\nsome poor guy's heart.
而你 是所有人里最明白其中滋味的
And you, you of all people\nknow exactly how that feels.
- 你真的不想说裤子糗事 对不?\n- 啥?
- You really don't want to tell the pants story,do you?\n- What?
裤子 裤子 裤子 裤...
Pants,pants,pants,pants,pants,\npants,pants, pants,pants,p-p...
好吧! 好
Fine! Okay?
然后 Lily来办公室帮我送裤子..
So,Lily came down to the\noffice to bring me my pants...
那她为啥要这么做?
And why did she have to do that?
因为我忘带裤子了
Because I forgot my pants.
Lily 你在这干吗?
Lily,what are you doing here?
我来给Marshal送点东西
Oh,I'm here to give Marshall something.
来这给他送点东西 明白 很好
Here togivehim something. Gotcha. Nice.
嗯 但我赶时间 给你成吗?
Yeah,but I-I'm in a hurry.\nCan I just give it to you?
成啊 好吧
Sure,okay.
然后你转交给他?
A\n- And then you'll give it to him?
等下 嘿 我不太明白
Wait,oh,hey. I don't\nknow about all that.
我是说 你得很厉害才行
I mean,yours would\nhave to be really good.
- 你在说啥呢?\n- 你在说啥?
- What are you talking about?\n- What are you talking about?
Marshall忘带裤子了 我给他送来一条
M\n- Marshall forgot his pants, so I'm bringing him a new pair.
Marshall忘带裤子了
Marshall forgot his pants.
你过来得真是时候\n他今天有个重要会议要开
Well,it's a good thing that you came by\nbecause he has a really important meeting today,
要是他不穿裤子开会
and it would be pretty\nembarrassing and not at all funny
就不是闹笑话的问题了\n简直会颜面扫地
if he were to show up not wearing pants.
- 我保证送到他手里\n- 太好了 谢谢 Barney
- So I'll make sure he gets these.\n- Great. Thanks,Barney.
但你没给他裤子
And you didn't give him his pants.
Theodore Evelyn Mosby\nTheodore Evelyn Mosby.
我当然给他裤子啦\n我向Lily保证过的 一诺千金
Of course I gave him his pants. I\ngave Lily my word. My word is oak.
只是我把裤子做了些改进
Though I did make some alterations.
现在 看合同第44页...
Now,as you'll see on\npage 44 of the contract...
嘿 Eriksen 你加入AC/DC了?\n(澳大利亚最著名的摇滚乐队)
Uh,hey,Eriksen, when did you join AC/DC?
现在 翻到合同第44页
Now,can we please just turn\nto page 44 of the contract.
嘿 Eriksen\n我想雾都孤儿的面试是在楼下吧!
Hey,Eriksen, I think theOliver\nTwist auditions are down the hall!
嘿 Eriksen 先生 能给我些裤子吗?
Hey,Eriksen, please,sir,may\nI have some more... pants?
再来点裤子...
More pan...
就这些? 整个故事就这些?
That's it? That's the whole story?
Karen后来咋样了?
So what happened with Karen?
我来为你继续
I'll finish it for you.
Ted无言地离去 \n而Karen再次得到自己想要的
Ted left without saying anything and\nKaren got exactly what she wanted.
这次不是
Not this time.
你有男友了?
So you have a boyfriend?
我们分居一段时间了
We've been drifting\napart for a long time.
我正想和他分手
I've been meaning to break up with him.
天哪 Karen 你太难以置信了
God,Karen, you are unbelievable.
你没勇气和这种正点的家伙分手的
You don't have the guts to break up\nwith someone like a decent human being,
所以别废话了
so instead you pull this crap.
好吧 你说对了
Okay,you're right.
我饱览群书 深究艺术
I'm great with books.\nI'm great with art.
我能鉴别法国红酒的葡萄生产地\n并且差距小于一英里 但...
I'm great with identifying French wines from\nwithin a mile of where the grapes are grown. But...
但我并不擅长直视\n别人的眼睛 说出真实想法
I'm really bad when it comes to looking someone in\nthe eye and telling them the truth about how I feel.
我们都不擅长这个 但...
Well,we're both bad at that. But...
我想我们得做些改变\n我先来吧 Karen
I think we both need to change.\nSo,um,why don't I go first? Karen...
你真是个狠心的人 我再也不要看见你\n再也不要和你说话了
you're a really hurtful and reckless person, and\nI never want to see you or speak to you again.
再见
Au revoir.
Ted 等等
Ted,wait.
其实 "再见"的意思是"再次相见"
Actually,"au revoir"means\n"until we see each other again."
我想你是说我们还会再见面?
So,I'm assuming that you mean we\nwill in fact see each other again?
抱歉 伙计
Sorry,bro.
- 真好\n- 谢谢 谢谢
- Yes.\n- Thank you. Thank you.
- 好极了\n- Ted 你真牛
- Bravo.\n- Ted,I am impressed with you.
你也是 Marshall 你整天都穿着这个?
You,too,Marshall. Have you\nbeen wearing those all day?
炫耀我的小腿呗
They show off my calves.
裤子糗事 再说遍
Pants story. Tell it again.
或许你给Karen打电话是好事
You know,maybe it was\ngood you called Karen.
绝对是 不仅对我 也对她有好处
It definitely was. And not\njust for me, but for her,too.
那天晚上后来 她向Jerry提出分手\n这可是以前她一直没有对我做到的
Later that night, she sat down with Jerry, and she\nhad the break-up talk she always avoided with me.
你们明白了吧 孩儿们\n当你难以启齿时 最好...
So you see,kids, sometimes when you have to have\na tough conversation, the best thing to do...
等下 等下
Wait a second. Wait a second.
你说永远不要和Karen说话了 对不?
You said you were never gonna\ntalk to Karen again,right?
嗯
Yeah.
那你咋知道她听取了你的意见
Then how do you know\nshe took your advice?
对 关于这...
Oh,right. Well,about that...
她和那哥们分手后 她打我电话
After she broke up with that\ndude,she called me, we went out,
我们看对眼了 然后又开始约会
we hooked up,and we've\nbeen dating ever since.
我们直视对方 这次不知咋的\n貌似感觉与众不同
We're really seeing eye to eye, and this time,\nI don't know,it just feels different somehow.
她来了 冷静点!
Here she comes now. Be cool!